Contact

lashlers@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/lreyesrn (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

PowerPoint

Microsoft Word

Microsoft Excel

Languages

Spanish (Limited Working)

Swahili (Limited Working)

Certifications

Basic Life Support for Healthcare Providers (BLS)

Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS)

Advanced Cardiovascular Life Support Experienced Provider (ACLS)

Certified Medical-Surgical Registered Nurse (CMSRN)

Colorado Nursing License

Laura Reyes

RN, BSN, CMSRN, CEN

Colorado Springs, Colorado

Summary

Compassionate skilled professional with 8+ years of diverse nursing experience. Specialized in emergency nursing with an emphasis on competency, teamwork, integrity, and continued education to contribute to optimal healthcare delivery. Self-driven and easily adaptive with extensive experience as a travel/registry nurse. Daisy Award recipient. Passionate about public/global health.

Summarized skills:

- -Provide direct patient care while developing and implementing best practice nursing care plans.
- -Committed to promoting safety and ensuring education of patients and families on medications, plan of care, disease processes, and healthy lifestyle promotion.
- -Diverse experience as a resource/travel nurse. Flexible & quickly adapt to new surroundings.
- -Serving as patient/family advocate while coordinating care with an interdisciplinary team.
- -Highly developed time management and communication skills.
- -Team player and leadership responsibilities of charge nurse and new graduate/new staff preceptor.
- -EPIC Super-user. Cerner and Sunrise experience.

Experience

UCHealth
Perioperative RN
October 2019 - December 2019 (3 months)

Colorado Springs, Colorado Area

Memorial Central- Outpatient/Inpatient Surgery at a 413-bed hospital. Level 1 trauma center.

Saint Joseph Hospital
ED Traveling Nurse
June 2019 - September 2019 (4 months)
Tucson, Arizona

Emergency nursing care. 486-bed hospital.

Banner Health
ED Traveling Nurse
October 2018 - March 2019 (6 months)
Tucson, AZ

Jan. 2019- Mar. 2019

Emergency nursing care. South campus. 245-bed teaching hospital. Level 4 trauma center.

Oct. 2018-Jan. 2019

Emergency nursing care. Main campus. 479-bed teaching hospital. Level 1 trauma center. Extension offered.

Saint Joseph's Hospital Registered Nurse Emergency Department November 2016 - September 2018 (1 year 11 months) Denver, CO

Emergency nursing care. 365-bed teaching hospital. Level 4 trauma center. Completed Metropolitan State University ED nurse internship program. Daisy Award recipient 2017. Clinical Ladder Level 3 completion. ED Sepsis team representative. ED Nurse Educator representing Saint Joseph Hospital via SCL Health- selected to teach in partnership with Arusha Luther Medical Center and Arusha College of Nursing in Tanzania, East Africa.

Allstaff Homecare Home Health Nurse January 2018 - August 2018 (8 months) Denver, Colorado

Home health care and case manager for veteran patients.

Exempla Good Samaritan Medical Center Travel RN August 2016 - November 2016 (4 months)

Page 2 of 5

Lafayette, Colorado

Medical-surgical inpatient care. 183-bed teaching hospital. Level 2 trauma center. Extension offered.

University of Colorado Anschutz Medical Campus Travel RN May 2016 - August 2016 (4 months)

Aurora, CO

Inpatient care specialized in respiratory disease including pulmonary hypertension, thoracic surgery, and ENT surgical populations. 620-bed teaching hospital. Level 1 trauma center. Extension offered.

Oro Valley Hospital Seasonal RN December 2015 - April 2016 (5 months) Tucson, Arizona

Inpatient care specialized in cardiac disease. 146-bed hospital. Level 4 trauma center. Extension and full time position offered.

Banner Staffing Services Registry RN October 2015 - March 2016 (6 months)

Tucson, Arizona

Inpatient care at Main/South campuses: medical-surgical, oncology, neurology, intermediate trauma, cardiac and respiratory intermediate care, orthopedics, telemetry, and transplant units. 479/245-bed teaching hospital. Level 1/Level 4 trauma centers.

Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center Travel RN July 2015 - October 2015 (4 months) New York, New York

Mohs Micrographic & Dermatological Outpatient Surgery RN. Assisted with Mohs surgery and procedures including excisions, laser therapy, and closures involving advanced skin flaps/grafts to treat skin cancer. Provide pre-op and post-op education and wound care/triage. Permanent position offered.

NYU Tisch Hospital Travel RN April 2015 - July 2015 (4 months) New York, New York Inpatient care specialized in pulmonary and cardiac disease. 725-bed teaching hospital. Level 1 trauma center. Extension offered.

Banner - University Medical Center 3 years 11 months

Resource RN April 2014 - July 2015 (1 year 4 months) Tucson, Arizona

Inpatient care at Main/South campuses: medical-surgical, oncology, neurology, intermediate trauma, cardiac and respiratory intermediate care, orthopedics, telemetry, and transplant units. 479/245-bed teaching hospital. Level 1/Level 4 trauma centers.

RN

September 2011 - April 2014 (2 years 8 months)

Medical Intermediate Care Unit

Completed new graduate nurse preceptorship. Originally hired for intermediate care unit (IMC), but due to delay in opening until Apr. 2012, oriented in observation and then floated inpatient: medical-surgical, oncology, neurology, intermediate trauma, cardiac and respiratory intermediate care, orthopedics, telemetry, and transplant units. 479-bed hospital. Level 1 trauma center.

Once the IMC unit opened in Apr. 2012, worked on intermediate care unit specializing in respiratory disease. Cared for high acuity patients including non-invasive ventilation, monitoring of insulin/vasoactive drips, tracheostomies, alcohol withdrawal, and Remodulin therapy. Charge RN and new graduate/ staff preceptor. Wound care unit representative.

Support for International Change Program Coordinator August 2010 - August 2011 (1 year 1 month)

University of Arizona, Tucson, AZ and Arusha/Babati, Tanzania, East Africa

At the University of Arizona, interviewed and selected cohesive team of volunteers. Prepared weekly curriculum to promote understanding of Tanzanian culture, HIV/AIDS education, and travel safety. Once in Tanzania, led 2 week orientation with both Americans and Tanzanians, organized teaching teams, supervised volunteers/Tanzanians in villages, promoted safety, and anticipated health needs. Organized community testing days, provided feedback on overall progress, and compiled reports.

The University of Arizona- Arizona Cancer Center Student Administrative Assistant January 2007 - May 2009 (2 years 5 months)

Tucson, Arizona Area

Assisted oncology doctors to answer calls, organize files, and office duties.

Education

University of Arizona

Bachelor of Science in Nursing (B.S.N.), Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2005 - 2011)